标记8，接近中
On mark 8 and closing.
稳定前进，相位炮待命
Steady as she goes. Phaser crew, stand by.
射程45,000公里，舰长
Range 45,000 kilometers, Captain.
真迷人
Fascinating.
射程43,000公里，接近中
Range 43,000 kilometers and closing.
- 传感器读数  - 一个未知的机械装置
- Sensor readings. - An unknown mechanical device.
我在船上没有读到生命形式
I read no life-forms aboard.
- 分析  - 显然是想拦截我们
- Analysis. - Obviously it intends to intercept us.
它跟着我们做了几次航线变化
It has made several course changes corresponding with our own.
38,000，接近中...35,000，接近中
38,000 and closing... 35,000 and closing.
不清楚它是打算攻击我们还是仅仅与我们交流
Unclear whether it intends to attack or merely communicate with us.
谢谢，科学官
Thank you, Science Officer.
- 前往181，标记7  - 是的，长官
- Come to 181, mark 7. - Aye, aye, sir.
- 它和我们在一起  - 的确
- It's staying with us. - Indeed.
- 完全停止，契科夫先生，原地待命  - 是的，长官
- Full stop, Mr. Chekov. Hold position. - Aye, sir.
梅尔克特：外星人
MELKOT: Aliens.
你已经侵占了梅尔克特的空间
You have encroached on the space of the Melkot.
你要立即掉头
You will turn back immediately.
这是你会收到的唯一警告
This is the only warning you will receive.
- 瓦肯语，舰长  - 英语
- Vulcan, Captain. - English.
- 是俄语，长官，每个词都是  - 不，是斯瓦希里语
- It was Russian, sir. Every word. - No, it was Swahili.
- 有趣，心灵感应  - 毫无疑问
- Interesting. Telepathy. - Unquestionably.
- 令人印象深刻  - 我们的命令很明确
- Most impressive. - Our orders are clear.
我们要不惜一切代价与梅尔克特人建立联系
We're to establish contact with the Melkotians at all costs.
真正的心灵感应者可能是最强大的，我们已经被警告过了
True telepaths can be most formidable, and we have been warned.
有过哪些接触？
What contacts have been made?
没有过接触，如果他们冒险进入太空，他们会立即撤离
None. If they ever ventured into space, they withdrew immediately.
上尉...
Lieutenant...
- 呼叫频率  - 已连接，长官
- Hailing frequencies. - Tied in, sir.
这是星舰企业号的詹姆斯·T·柯克舰长
This is Captain James T. Kirk of the starship Enterprise,
来自星际联邦
from the United Federation of Planets.
我们了解你的浮标所传达的信息
We understand your buoy's message.
我们的目的是与您建立和平关系
Our intent is to establish peaceful relations with you.
- 有回应吗？  - 没有，所有的频率都很清楚
- Answer? - Nothing. Clear on all frequencies.
再试一次
Try again.
仍然没有回应，长官
Still no response, sir.
有何意见，史波克先生？
Opinion, Mr. Spock?
我更喜欢做一个受欢迎的客人，但似乎别无选择
I prefer being a welcome guest. But there seems to be little choice.
一点也没有，契科夫先生，防护罩调到最大强度
None whatsoever. Mr. Chekov, deflectors to full intensity.
- 提高速度登陆  - 五分钟内进入标准轨道
- Increase speed to achieve planetfall. - Standard orbit in five minutes.
让麦考伊医生和轮机长斯科特在传送室与我碰头
Advise Dr. McCoy and Engineer Scott to meet me in the transporter room.
史波克，契科夫，我们去看看他们在害怕什么
Spock, Chekov, let's go find out what they're afraid of.
柯克：舰长日志，星历4385.3
KIRK: Captain's log, stardate 4385.3.
我们来到了梅尔克特星球
We have come to the Melkotian planet
并且遇到了我们没有准备的情况
and have encountered conditions which we weren't prepared for.
- 这是什么？  - 未知
- What is this? - Unknown.
传感器读数没有显示类似雾的情况
Sensor readings give no indication of fog-like conditions.
通讯器坏得真是时候
It's a fine time for the transporter mechanism to break down.
不可能，我的通讯器工作正常
Impossible. My transporter was working perfectly.
- 那我们在这里做什么？  - 读数呢？
- Then what are we doing here? - Readings?
未知，舰长，这个东西不工作
Unknown, Captain. This unit is not functioning.
那我们离开这里吧
Then let's get out of here.
柯克呼叫企业号，柯克呼叫企业号，请回答
Kirk to Enterprise. Kirk to Enterprise. Come in.
没用，我们的设备都不工作
No use. None of our devices will function.
- 显然那个梅尔克特浮标...- 外星人...
- Apparently that Melkotian buoy... - Aliens...
柯克：宇宙，最后的边疆
KIRK: Space, the final frontier.
这些是星舰企业号的航程
These are the voyages of the starship Enterprise.
它的五年任务：探索未知的新世界
Its five-year mission: To explore strange new worlds,
寻找新生命和新文明
to seek out new life and new civilizations,
勇踏前人未至之境
to boldly go where no man has gone before.
我们的警告很明确，你忽略了它
Our warning was plain. You have disregarded it.
你要受到惩罚
You shall be punished.
你，柯克舰长，不服从是奉你的命令
You, Captain Kirk. The disobedience was on your orders.
责任在你
Yours is the responsibility.
你将是你们死亡的模式
Yours shall be the pattern of your death.
我们为和平而来，但如果有必要，我们会自卫
We come in peace. But we'll defend ourselves if necessary.
你们是外来的，你们是疾病
You are outside. You are disease.
必须消灭疾病
The disease must be destroyed.
你们的请求已被听取，判决已宣布
Your plea has been heard, and sentence has been pronounced.
结束了
It is done.
真有趣
Fascinating.
我们现在在哪里，舰长？
Where are we now, Captain?
史波克，评估
Spock, evaluation.
这是梅尔克特人概念里的美国边陲小镇
This represents the Melkotian's concept of an American frontier town,
大约1880年
Circa 1880.
这只是些零碎的东西，不完整
It's just bits and pieces. It's incomplete.
也许梅尔克特人没有足够的关于这个时代的数据
Perhaps the Melkotians have insufficient data about this era.
或许这就是他们完成我们死亡的模式所需要的一切
Or perhaps this is all they require to complete the pattern of our death.
还有这些，舰长？
And these, Captain?
- 美丽的标本  - 粗糙但危险
- Beautiful specimen. - Crude but dangerous.
无论梅尔克特人有什么计划，都不会令人愉快
Whatever the Melkotians have planned, it won't be pleasant.
这些可能有用
These could be useful.
但对于近距离的人来说，这些可能和相位枪一样致命
But to individuals at close range, these could be as deadly as phasers.
在看似如此不真实的事物中，却是残酷的现实，这不是梦
In the midst of what seems so unreal, a harsh reality. This is not a dream.
[门砰砰响]
[DOOR BANGS]
1881年10月26日
October 26th, 1881.
柯克：亚利桑那州，墓碑镇
KIRK: Tombstone, Arizona.
墓碑镇，勇往直前，源于历史
Tombstone. Hell for leather, right out of history.
但为什么是这里？
But why here?
- 为什么是现在？  - 梅尔克特说你就是模式
- And why now? - The Melkot said you were the pattern.
他洞察了你的思维，选择了惩罚我们的时间和地点
He looked into your mind and selected a time and place for our punishment.
因为我的祖先开拓了美国边疆
Because my ancestors pioneered the American frontier.
你继承自祖先的暴力将成为我们死刑的模式
The violence of your own heritage is to be the pattern for our execution.
我们说得好像我们真的在1881年亚利桑那州的墓碑镇
We're talking like we really are in Tombstone, Arizona in 1881.
确切地说，就梅尔科特人的意图而言
Precisely, in terms of what the Melkots intend.
那个日期有事，1881年10月26日
There's something about that date. October 26th, 1881.
但是什么事呢？
But what was it?
艾克！
Ike!
艾克！弗兰克！比利！汤姆！我还在担心你不会成功呢
Ike! Frank! Billy! Tom! I was afraid you weren't going to make it.
- 我们做到了  - 我就知道他们不会把你吓跑的
- We did. - I knew they wouldn't scare you away.
他们就是一群吹牛大王
They're a bunch of hot air.
- 真的吗？  - 现在他们要打架了
- Are they really? - Now they'll have to fight.
你认识我们吗？
Do you know us?
有趣！这就是我喜欢你的地方，你总能看到有趣的一面
Funny! That's what I like about you. You always see the funny side.
我是个笑料十足的人。
I'm a barrel of laughs.
约翰尼·贝汉很有幽默感
Johnny Behan has a sense of humor.
约翰尼…？
Johnny...?
他叫我艾克，叫你弗兰克，叫骨头汤姆
He called me Ike, you Frank, Bones Tom.
还有比利...
And Billy...
艾克·克兰顿、汤姆和弗兰克·麦克劳里
Ike Clanton, Tom and Frank McLowery,
比利·克莱伯恩，比利·克兰顿
Billy Claiborne, Billy Clanton.
我为自己对地球历史的了解而自豪
I pride myself on my knowledge of Earth history.
这些名字在美国西部开发的编年史中广为人知
The names were known in the annals of the opening of the American West.
美利坚合众国，就是这样
The United States of America, that is.
在19世纪后期的亚利桑那州
In the late 19th Century in Arizona,
两个派系争夺墓碑镇的控制权
two factions fought for control of the town of Tombstone.
厄普兄弟，摩根、维吉尔和怀亚特，是镇上的执法官
The Earps, Morgan, Virgil and Wyatt, the town marshals.
- 与多克·霍利德  - 还有克兰顿帮
- Along with Doc Holliday. - And the Clanton gang.
10月26日，他们进行了火拼
On October 26th, they had it out.
谁赢了？
Who won?
克兰顿兄弟输了
The Clantons lost.
而我们是克兰顿兄弟？
And we are the Clantons?
我们是克兰顿兄弟，如果这是历史的重演……
We are the Clantons. And if this is a replay of history...
历史无法改变
History cannot be changed.
[木头碎片]
[WOOD SPLINTERS]
不可能！这样的事情是不可能发生的
It's impossible! Things like this can't happen.
- 这是一个死人吗，医生？  - 死透了，史波克先生
- Is this a dead man, Doctor? - Very dead, Mr. Spock.
在这儿我们可以确定一件事
That's one thing we can be sure of here.
死亡是真实的
Death is real.
[钢琴演奏]
[PIANO PLAYS]
小伙子们，你们好吗？我没想到我会再见到你
How are you, boys? I didn't think I'd see you again.
女人：比利！
WOMAN: Billy!
哦，比利！
Oh, Billy!
我就知道他们不能把你赶走
I knew they couldn't keep you away.
- 你知道？  - 拜托
- You knew that? - Come on.
- 也许你不该在这儿  - 错过见你的机会？
- Maybe you shouldn't have. - And miss the chance to see you?
这是疯狂的冒险，摩根·厄普在这里
It's taking crazy chances with Morgan Earp here.
是的，当然，那人见人就杀
Yes, of course. The man who kills on sight.
摩根·厄普
Morgan Earp.
既然我们已经看到死亡是这种情况下的一个现实
Since we have seen that death is the one reality in this situation,
我郑重建议你重新找个位置
I seriously suggest you reseat yourself.
两只手都不要动
Without moving a muscle of either hand.
否则将使你卷入所谓的“快速拔枪”
That would involve you in what was called "the fast draw".
它引发了不幸的事件
It initiated unfortunate events.
- 你们要和平常一样的吗？  - 是的，半加仑苏格兰威士忌
- You boys want your usual? - Yes. A half a gallon of Scotch.
你知道我们只有波旁威士忌，或玉米威士忌
You know we only got bourbon. Or corn whiskey.
我希望一切都结束了，我今天早上看到维吉尔在外面巡逻
I wish it was all over. I saw Virgil out patrolling this morning.
我们总是可以指望维吉尔
We can always count on Virgil.
他们一直吹嘘要把克兰顿兄弟赶出去
They've been boasting about chasing the Clantons out.
我猜你现在要给他们点颜色看看，是吗？
I guess you'll show them now, won't you?
我认为我们没有任何选择
I don't think we're going to have any choice.
- 别让这个人渣玷污了你  - 别碰她！
- You'll dirty yourself with this scum. - Get your hands off her!
好吧，我们不想惹任何麻烦
All right. We don't want any trouble.
- 那你来我的镇上做什么？  - 别烦我们，厄普先生
- Then what are you doing in my town? - Just leave us alone, Mr. Earp.
你们五个，你们希望我拔枪，不是吗？好的，我会的
Five of you. You'd like me to draw, wouldn't you? All right. I will.
很快
Soon enough.
我相信他实际上是想挑起与契科夫先生的争端
I believe he was actually trying to provoke a dispute with Mr. Chekov.
真险，艾克，幸好他们不是两个人
Close, Ike. Lucky there wasn't two of them.
大概吧
I guess so.
西尔维亚说得对，他们一直在恶语相向
Sylvia's right. They've been badmouthing something fierce.
你们看着点
You boys watch it.
我们会盯着的，密切观察一切
We shall watch it, and everything, extremely closely.
比利，你真好
Billy, you were wonderful.
呃……契科夫先生？
Um... Mr. Chekov?
你知道我们总是应该与当地人保持良好的关系
You know we're always supposed to maintain good relations with natives.
小姐...
Young lady...
小姐...- 是的，艾克
- Young lady... - Yes, Ike.
如果你不介意的话，我想单独和先生...比利谈谈
I'd like to talk to Mr... to Billy alone if you don't mind.
好的，我明白
All right. I understand.
比利·克莱伯恩，你要小心
Billy Claiborne, you be careful.
契科夫先生，你要小心
Mr. Chekov, you be careful.
史波克先生，除了我们的手枪，我们没有改变
Mr. Spock, except for our handguns, we haven't changed.
- 还有他们将我们视为克兰顿兄弟  - 我不认为那是件坏事
- Yet they see us as the Clantons. - I don't think that's such a bad thing.
- 时间还早  - 我们知道什么？
- The day is still young. - What have we got?
我们在1881年10月26日的亚利桑那州的墓碑镇
We're in Tombstone, Arizona, October 26th, 1881.
OK畜栏枪战那天，而我们是克兰顿兄弟
The day of the gunfight at OK Corral. And we're the Clantons.
摩根·厄普去告诉他的兄弟们我们在这儿
Morgan Earp is telling his brothers we're here.
如果这是某种历史重演
And if this is some sort of a replay of history,
厄普兄弟将在今天下午5:00在OK畜栏杀死克兰顿兄弟
the Earps will kill the Clantons at the OK Corral at 5:00 this afternoon.
今天下午5:00我们不要去OK畜栏
We're not going to be at the OK Corral at 5:00 this afternoon.
你，酒保，埃德，你呃…你说你认识我们
You. Bartender. Ed. You er... you claim you know us.
我没有夸大其词，就这么发生了
I ain't making no big claims. It just so happens.
- 仔细看看我  - 是的
- Take a close look at me. - Yeah.
- 你觉得我是谁？  - 艾克·克兰顿，你认为是谁？
- Who do you think I am? - Ike Clanton. Who do you think?
我知道这难以理解，但我是詹姆斯·T·柯克舰长
I know this is hard to understand, but I'm Captain James T. Kirk.
这些人是我的船员，我们不是真的在这里，我们来自未来
These men are my crew. We're not really here. We're from the future.
我们还没有出生
We haven't been born yet.
摸摸我衬衫的布料
Feel the material in my shirt.
现在摸摸你衬衫的布料
Now feel the material in your own shirt.
你注意到有什么不同吗？
Do you notice any difference?
没有
No.
- 这些衣服看起来和你的像吗？  - 不完全像
- Do these clothes look like yours? - Not exactly.
- 你见过这样的衣服吗？  - 当然，在克兰顿家的人身上
- Have you ever seen clothes like this? - Sure. On the Clantons.
- 你们克兰顿家的人很会开玩笑  - 我不是在开玩笑
- You Clantons are great with jokes. - I'm not joking.
厄普家的人从不开玩笑
The Earps never joke.
我不是在开玩笑！我不是艾克·克兰顿！
I'm not joking! I'm not Ike Clanton!
随你怎么说，艾克，我认为你是谁并不重要
Anything you say, Ike. Don't matter who I think you are.
你的问题是，怀亚特·厄普认为你是谁？
Your problem is, who does Wyatt Earp think you are?
早上好，我是詹姆斯·柯克，这里有个误会
Good morning. I'm James Kirk. There's been a misunderstanding.
我不知道你想耍什么花招，
I don't know what you're trying to pull,
但我们警告过你别再在镇上露出你的丑恶嘴脸了
but we warned you not to show your ugly face in town again.
- 我想和你谈谈这个  - 我们谈完了，克兰顿
- I wanted to talk to you about that. - We're done talking, Clanton.
- 但这里有个误会，我...- 再给你一次机会，最后一次
- But there's been a mistake. I... - One more chance. Your last.
你必须在今晚5:00之前让你的偷马队出城
You've got until 5:00 tonight to get your horse-stealing crew out of town.
沿着路一直走
All the way.
- 是的，我们不想打架  - 我一直说你胆小
- Yes. We don't want a fight. - I always said you was yellow.
我想再次试着使你理解
I'll make one more attempt to get through to you.
我不叫克兰顿，我叫柯克
My name is not Clanton. It's Kirk.
- 我们听到了你的笑话  - 我不是在开玩笑
- We heard the talk about your jokes. - I'm not joking.
当然，好吧，很高兴见到你，柯克先生
Sure. Well, I'm glad to meet you, Mr. Kirk.
- 拔枪，克兰顿  - 不是我，厄普先生
- Draw, Clanton. - Not me, Mr. Earp.
- 不是你你拔枪就是我拔枪  - 不，怀亚特
- You draw or I will. - No, Wyatt.
让我来，时机一到，我会让他付出代价
Let me. When the time comes, I'll pay him for this.
我们不想有任何麻烦，我们会合作的
We don't want any trouble. We'll cooperate.
5:00，克兰顿，明白了吗？
5:00, Clanton. Is that clear?
如果你在5:01在城里，我们会杀了你们每个人，不管你拔不拔枪
If you're in town at 5:01, we'll kill every one of you whether you draw or not.
明白了吗？
Is that clear?
- 怎么了？  - 他们怎么称呼那种东西？火？
- What's the matter? - What do they call that stuff? Fire?
陶斯闪电，试试看，它被认为是药用的
Taos Lightning. Try some. It was considered medicinal.
他们应该给它贴上标签，“仅供外用”
They ought to label it, "For external use only."
需要一点时间适应，事实上，人会慢慢喜欢上它
It just takes a bit of getting used to. Actually, a man could grow fond of it.
我不愿去想它对你的胃有什么影响。
I hate to think what it's doing to your stomach.
还有你的反应速度，从现在开始，我们需要快速反应
And your reflexes. We'll need fast reflexes from now on.
- 没有与厄普兄弟谈判  - 是的，要是我们有一把相位枪
- There's no negotiating with the Earps. - Aye. If we only had a phaser.
或者通讯器
Or a communicator.
当我们被传送回船上时，看厄普兄弟的反应会很有趣
It would be a pleasure to watch those Earps as we beamed back to the ship.
- 我们可以做一个吗？  - 不可能的
- Could we make one? - Impossible.
没有金属合金或能源来制造我们的设备
There are no metal alloys or power sources to make our devices.
我们得要寻找同时代的解决方案
We're going to have to seek contemporary solutions.
- 契科夫呢？-契科夫先生在恋爱
- Where's Chekov? - Mr. Chekov is involved.
你不应该回镇里
You shouldn't have come back to town.
摩根会杀了你，因为他想要得到我
Morgan will kill you because he wants me.
用他过时的武器？
With his outdated weapon?
如果他向我开枪，我让开就行了
If he shoots at me, I'll just step out of the way.
你可以拿它开玩笑，我见过他们的行动，尤其是摩根
You can joke about it. I've seen them in action. Especially Morgan.
很多人和事都试图杀死我，你会惊讶的
A lot of people and things have tried to kill me. You'd be surprised.
契科夫先生……我是说比利，来吧
Mr. Chekov... I mean Billy. Come along.
是的，长官
Yes, sir.
比利？
Billy?
拜托，不要靠近他
Please. Don't even go near him.
先生们
Gentlemen.
- 我们去哪？  - 锻炼一下勇气
- Where are we going? - To exercise the better part of valor.
问题解决了，一个力场
That settles that. A force field.
[钟声]
[CLOCK CHIMES]
梅尔克特人不会允许我们离开这个城镇
The Melkotians are not going to permit us to leave this town.
- 如果我们能和飞船取得联系就好了  - 但它在哪儿？
- If we could only contact the ship. - But where is it?
如果是你在操控，你会做什么？
If you were in charge of it, what would you be doing?
我会使用传感器，试图定位我们
I'd be using the sensors, trying to locate us.
很好，如果我们能找我们到被传送下来的地方
Good. If we could find the place where we beamed down,
飞船可能会传送我们上去
the ship might beam us up.
- 让我们到那里去  - 我们不知道它在哪里
- Let's get there. - We can't know where it is.
1,000英里内的任何地方
Anywhere within 1,000 miles.
史波克，试着找出一条出去的路，别再解释我们为什么不能出去了
Spock, try to find a way out and quit explaining why we can't get out.
考虑到我们必须在5:00之前找到那个方法
We have until 5:00 to find that way. Consider this.
手头有哪些1881年的材料
What materials were on hand in 1881
可以帮助我们按照厄普兄弟的方式来对抗他们？
that could help us fight the Earps on their own terms?
- 我们有这些  - 他们给我们那些东西来处决我们
- We have these. - They gave us those to execute us.
我们必须让厄普兄弟停止活动
We have to put the Earps out of action.
现在有什么东西可以帮助我们摆脱这个陷阱吗？
Does anything exist here and now that could help us out of this trap?
那些西部哥萨克只有毒蛇和仙人掌植物
Those Western Cossacks only had poisonous snakes and cactus plants.
老骨头，毒液，植物，你能利用它们吗？
Bones, the venom, the plants. Can you make use of them?
当然！我可以做镇静剂！
Of course! I can make a tranquilizer!
我可以制作一个装置来释放它
I could make a device to deliver it.
你需要的原料有什么？
The ingredients you require?
我知道哪里可以买到合适的药物
I know the place to get the proper drugs.
- 我需要研钵和研杵  - 契科夫
- I'll need a mortar and a pestle. - Chekov.
你将如何提供镇静剂？
How will you deliver the tranquilizer?
- 我需要引信和棉絮  - 试试药房
- I'll need fusing and cotton wadding. - Try the apothecary.
我将制造类似老式引发罐的东西
I shall manufacture the equivalent of an ancient generating canister,
更广为人知的名称是毒气手榴弹
more familiarly known as a gas grenade.
我还要等五分钟左右。你可以回来了
I'll be about five minutes yet. You could come back.
谢谢你，介意我环顾四周吗？
Thank you. Mind if I look around a bit?
- 粗糙但非常有用  - 我不会碰那些东西
- Crude but very usable. - I wouldn't touch that stuff.
我知道如何处理这个
I know how to handle this.
我也急需少量的这种药物
I have an urgent need for a small supply of this drug, too.
那是他的，你最好问问他
That belongs to him. You'd better ask him.
所以你是牙医？嗯，我是一名医生
So you're the dentist? Well, I'm a physician.
我想知道你是否介意我借一点这个
I wonder if you'd mind if I borrowed a small quantity of this.
- 你现在要吗？  - 我叫麦考伊，我医生
- You want it now? - My name is McCoy. I'm a doctor.
这个笑话已经传遍整个小镇了，麦克洛韦里
That joke is all around town already, McLowery.
但我的名字仍然是霍利德
But my name is still Holliday.
多克·霍利德
Doc Holliday.
…紧急情况是真的，我需要这些东西
The... emergency is real. I need these things.
你的紧急情况肯定是真的
Your emergency sure is real.
去吧，拿上东西，多找点乐子
Go on. Take the stuff. Have some more fun.
拿上我的包
Take my bag.
你最好在5:00之前完成
Only best you be finished before 5:00.
那是我想要的，医生
That is my intention, Doctor.
因为在五点零一分，你会发现你的脑袋有一个洞
Because at one minute past five, you'll find a hole in your head.
用这把枪打的
Right from this gun.
[清嗓子]
[CLEARS THROAT]
西尔维亚！
Sylvia!
你好
Hello.
比利，你知道我对你有多痴迷吗？
Billy, do you know how crazy I am about you?
那...真不错
That's... very nice.
你不问问我包里有什么吗？
Aren't you going to ask what's in my bag?
这正是我准备要问的
That's just what I was preparing to inquire.
你去购物了吗？
Have you been shopping?
当然，在一个美好的下午，我还能做什么
Of course. What else would I be doing on a beautiful afternoon,
距离舞会只有一周了？
with the dance only one week away?
- 还是说你已经忘记了？  - 不，我没忘记
- Or have you forgotten that already? - No, I haven't forgotten.
我很期待……非常期待
I am looking forward to it... most eagerly.
当我穿着我要做的礼服时你绝对会疯狂
You'll be absolutely wild when you see me in the gown I'm going to make.
我找到了了这种最绝妙的料子，有很多码
I found this most scrumptious material. Yards and yards of it.
你知道我在想什么吗，比利？
You know what I was thinking, Billy?
我在想它能做一件多么漂亮的婚纱啊
I was thinking what a beautiful wedding gown it would make.
我们为什么不把那场舞会变成婚礼舞会呢？
Why don't we turn that dance into a wedding ball?
那将是无比美好的
It would be so heavenly.
结婚？
Married?
恐怕……那不可能
I'm afraid... that wouldn't be possible.
我有把握会准备好礼服，还有什么能阻止我们？
But I'm positive the gown will be ready. What else is there to stop us?
这是绝对不可能的，我不是你可以嫁的人
It is absolutely impossible. I am not someone you can marry.
如果我能告诉你……我的真实身份就好了
If only I could make clear to you... what I really am.
你以为我不知道吗？
Do you think I don't know?
比利·克莱伯恩，你是个偷牛贼和偷马贼
Billy Claiborne, you are a cattle rustler and a horse thief
我不在乎其他的
and I don't care what else.
我警告过你，克莱伯恩，离远点
I warned you, Claiborne. Stay away.
[西尔维亚尖叫]
[SYLVIA SCREAMS]
我在这里的时候，你不必从那个人渣那里拿任何东西
You don't have to take anything from that scum while I'm here.
厄普先生，别碰她
Mr. Earp. Get your hands off her.
[尖叫]
[SCREAMS]
我无能为力，吉姆
There's nothing I can do, Jim.
来吧，克兰顿，现在就决斗吧
Come on, Clanton. Let's do it now.
- 舰长，让我来  - 是的，拜托，舰长，让他来
- Captain, let me. - Yeah, come on, Captain. Let him.
- 我们不能只是站在这里  - 我们可以
- We can't just stand here. - Yes, we can.
- 但他们谋杀了契科夫！- 斯科提
- But they murdered Chekov! - Scotty.
- 他们想逼我们  - 现在还不是我们的时间
- They're trying to push us. - And it is not yet our time.
算了吧，他死了
Let it go. He's dead.
因为我忽略了梅尔克特警告
Because I ignored the Melkot warning.
我们在入伍时都知道有风险，现在让它过去吧
We all knew the risk when we joined the service. Now let it go.
有一件事需要我们立即注意
There is one thing which requires our immediate attention,
具体来说，是我们的未来
specifically, our future.
但不是这一刻，史波克
But not this minute, Spock.
我们需要更长的时间
It takes us a little longer.
我理解这种感受，舰长
I understand the feeling, Captain.
你谈论另一个人的感受，你感受到了什么？
You talk about another man's feelings. What do you feel?
我的感情不是讨论的话题
My feelings are not a subject for discussion.
- 没有感情可谈  - 斯波克先生，契科夫死了！
- There are no feelings to discuss. - Mr. Spock, Chekov is dead!
我现在说出来了，但还是难以相信
I say it now and I can hardly believe it.
但他值得一些纪念
But he deserves some memorial.
史波克不会悲伤，斯科提，悲伤是种人性
Spock will have no truck with grief, Scotty. It's human.
- 老骨头，斯科提...  - 舰长，没关系
- Bones, Scotty... - Captain, it's quite all right.
他们忘记了我是半个人类
They forget I am half human.
[钟声]
[CLOCK CHIMES]
我们没有太多时间
We don't have much time.
我依稀记得我们即将参加的战斗的报道
I vaguely remember the account of the battle in which we are about to engage.
- 但我很困惑  - 关于什么？
- But I am confused. - About what?
既然我们每个人都代表克兰顿帮的成员--
Since each of us represents members of the Clanton gang --
你是艾克·克兰顿，我是弗兰克·麦克劳里
you Ike Clanton, I Frank McLowery --
那么契科夫先生就是另一个比利，不是吗？
then Mr. Chekov would be the other Billy, would he not?
- 威廉·克莱伯恩  - 但是，威廉·克莱伯恩
- William Claiborne. - But did not William Claiborne
不是在OK畜栏的战斗中幸存下来了吗？
survive the battle at the OK Corral?
说重点，史波克
Get to the point, Spock.
契科夫先生死了，但在实际的枪战中，威廉·克莱伯恩活了下来
Mr. Chekov is dead. But in the actual gunfight, William Claiborne survived.
是的，是的，这是正确的
Yes. Yes, that's right.
所以不是非得按原来的情况发生，我们可以改变它
So it doesn't have to happen the way it happened. We can change it.
进展如何？  - 我会在史波克之前做好准备
- How's that coming? - I'll be ready before Spock.
- 史波克？  - 还有一个小时
- Spock? - Another hour.
- 我们会有手榴弹？  - 不准确
- We'll have a grenade? - Not precisely.
- 别管叫法了，它能行吗？  - 应该可以
- Forget precision. Will it work? - It should.
如果我们不让他们镇静下来，我们就必须与他们战斗
If we don't tranquilize them, we'll have to fight them.
如果我们与他们战斗，我们都会死
And if we fight them, we all die.
谈判可以为我们赢得时间
Negotiating could buy us time.
但不是和厄普兄弟，我试过了，一定有办法的
But not with the Earps. I've tried that. There must be a way.
历史已经改变，克莱伯恩没死，但契科夫死了
History has been changed. Claiborne didn't die but Chekov is dead.
这意味着这次一定有办法改变
That means there must be a way to change this time.
值得一试，至少在我们对设备有把握之前
It would be worth a try, at least until we're certain of the device.
然后也许我们可以让事情平息下来
Then perhaps we could quiet things down.
不是和厄普兄弟
Not with the Earps.
还有一个地方我可以试试
There is one other place I can try.
你在找人吗？
You looking for somebody?
是的，警长
Yes, Sheriff.
- 我要你阻止冲突  - 阻止它？
- I want you to stop the fight. - Stop it?
谁想阻止它？我肯定不想，你也不想
Who wants to stop it? I sure don't. You don't.
- 你昨天还不想的  - 我现在想了
- You didn't yesterday. - I do now.
一个克兰顿家的人何时学会向法律求助了？
When does a Clanton crawl to the law for help?
- 他还能怎样伸张正义？  - 用这个
- How else can he get justice? - From this.
你安排这整件事是为了解决厄尔普家族的事
You set up this whole thing to take care of the Earps.
- 决定反对它为时已晚  - 不算太晚
- It's too late to decide against it. - It's not too late.
警长，警长
Sheriff. Sheriff.
让我们把不喜欢厄普兄弟的人组织起来
Let's organize the people who don't like the Earps.
不要胡说八道，他们指望你们除掉厄普兄弟
Don't talk nonsense. They're counting on you to get rid of the Earps.
他们最好让法律为他们所用
They'd better let the law work for them.
今天厄尔普家族对比利做了那样的事，你还能这样说话？
You can talk that way after what the Earps did to Billy today?
这个镇上没有人会拒绝你报仇的权利
Nobody in this town will deny you your right to your revenge.
是的，我要复仇，我想取厄普一家的命
Yes, I want revenge. I want to crush the life out of the Earps.
- 但我不能只是杀了他们  - 你听我说
- But I can't just kill them. - You listen to me.
躲在OK畜栏
Hide at the OK Corral.
当厄普兄弟来找你时，你伏击他们
When the Earps come looking, you bushwhack them.
- 我不能这样杀了他们！- 这是唯一的办法！
- I can't just kill them! - It's the only way!
我不能谋杀他们！我不能杀他们！
I can't murder them! I can't kill them!
尽你所能杀死他们！
Kill them any way you can!
不会有任何问题，真的
There will be no questions asked. Honest.
我保证
I guarantee that.
这些原油效果相当好
These crude supplies worked quite well.
我怀疑这些东西曾经被用于这样的目的
I doubt these things were ever used for any purpose like this.
如果他们有你的聪明才智，也许他们会这样做
Perhaps they would have been if they'd had your ingenuity.
舰长？
Captain?
- 多久能准备好？  - 就现在
- How soon will that be ready? - Right now.
镇静剂要多久才能起作用？
How long until the tranquilizer works?
- 三秒钟  - 你是怎么测试的？
- Three seconds. - How did you test it?
- 没有测试过  - 这很简单，什么都不会出错
- It has not been tested. - It's simple. Nothing can go wrong.
到现在为止，一切都出错了，我要测试一下
Up to now, everything has gone wrong. I want it tested.
志愿者能解决问题吗？
Would a volunteer solve the problem?
- 能  - 好吧，有一个条件
- It would. - All right. On one condition.
我和你要在5:00前清醒
That I'm wide awake and with you at 5:00.
- 我保证  - 好的
- Guaranteed. - All right.
这是为了止痛
It's to kill the pain.
- 但这是无痛的  - 你应该早点告诉我的
- But this is painless. - You should have warned me sooner.
开始吧
Fire away.
- 它应该有用，你吸气了吗？  - 是的，深吸气了
- It should work. Did you inhale? - Aye. Deeply.
- 你还觉得好吗？  - 再好不过了
- You still feel all right? - Never felt better.
- 没有头晕？出汗？  - 它没有用
- No dizziness? Sweating? - It doesn't work.
- 真有趣  - 这是我们最后的机会
- Fascinating. - It was our last chance.
队长，你好像没听懂
Captain, you don't seem to understand.
它没有起作用，但它一定是有效的
It did not function, but it must function.
不会出错的，它应该有效的
Nothing could go wrong. It should work.
一个科学事实
A scientific fact.
但如果镇静剂不起作用
But if the tranquilizer does not function,
那么就必须改变我们的思维模式了
then an alteration of our thought patterns must be in order.
我们需要一把武器，一个解决办法
We need a weapon. An answer.
现在不必担心这个，看看钟
Don't have to worry about that now. Look at the clock.
10分钟，这一切都将在OK畜栏结束
Ten minutes. It's all going to end at the OK Corral.
我们要在这里等到5:00以后
We're going to wait right here until well after 5:00.
我们不会离开这个地方
We're not going to move from this spot.
[马嘶声]
[HORSE NEIGHS]
我们离开这里吧！
Let's get out of here!
斯科提，老骨头
Scotty, Bones.
我们被困住了
We're trapped.
他们如愿以偿，我们必须站起来战斗
They got their way. We've got to stand and fight.
好的，如果他们想打架，那就打吧
Good. If they want a fight, let's give them a fight.
他们是专家，我们不会有机会了
They're experts. We won't have a chance.
- 我们最好成为专家  - 那可能没有必要
- We'd better become experts. - That may not be necessary.
- 你想到什么了吗？  - 一个事实
- You've got something? - A fact.
物理定律是不容忽视的
Physical laws simply cannot be ignored.
没有他们就不能存在
Existence cannot be without them.
- 你是什么意思？  - 我们面临着矛盾
- What do you mean? - We are faced with a contradiction.
你创造的镇静剂应该是有效的
The tranquilizer you created should have been effective.
- 它在任何地方都该有效  - 确实
- It would have been anywhere else. - Exactly.
医生，在您看来，是什么杀死了契科夫先生？
Doctor, in your opinion, what killed Mr. Chekov?
- 他体内的一块铅  - 错
- A piece of lead in his body. - Wrong.
- 他的意识杀死了他  - 如果你有答案，告诉我们！
- His mind killed him. - If you've got the answer, tell us!
物理现实符合普遍规律
The physical reality is consistent with universal laws.
当定律不起作用时，就没有现实
When the laws do not operate, there is no reality.
这一切都是不真实的
All of this is unreal.
你是什​​么意思？我检查了契科夫，他死了
What do you mean? I examined Chekov. He's dead.
你在我们无法信任的条件下进行了检查
You made your examination under conditions we cannot trust.
我们通过感官的反应来判断现实
We judge reality by the response of our senses.
一旦我们确信某种情况的真实性
Once we are convinced of the reality of a situation,
我们遵守它的规则
we abide by its rules.
我们判断子弹是实心的，枪支是真实的
We judge the bullets to be solid, the guns to be real.
因此，他们可以杀人
Therefore, they can kill.
契科夫死了是因为他相信子弹会杀死他？
Chekov is dead because he believed the bullets would kill him?
他可能真的死了，我们不知道
He may indeed be dead. We do not know.
但我们确实知道，梅尔克特人创造了这个环境
But we do know that the Melkotians created the situation.
如果我们不相信子弹是真实的，它们就不能杀死我们
If we do not believe that the bullets are real, they cannot kill us.
确实如此，我知道子弹是不真实的，因此它们不能伤害我
Exactly. I know the bullets are unreal, therefore they cannot harm me.
我们必须都非常确定才能救我们的性命
We must all be certain to save our lives.
- 不错  - 但那是不可能的
- Precisely. - But that's not possible.
- 总会有一些疑问  - 一丁点儿怀疑都会要了你的命
- There would always be some doubt. - The smallest doubt would kill you.
我们只是人类，史波克，我们没有你的发条心脏
We're just human beings, Spock. We don't have your clockwork ticker.
- 我们不能打开和关闭它  - 必须要
- We can't turn it on and off. - We must.
史波克，瓦肯的心灵融合
Spock, a Vulcan mind-meld.
很好，长官，轮机长？
Very well, sir. Engineer?
你的意识到我的意识
Your mind to my mind.
你的想法到我的想法
Your thoughts to my thoughts.
子弹是不真实的
The bullets are unreal.
没有实体
Without body.
它们只是幻觉
They are illusions only.
没有实质的阴影
Shadows without substance.
它们不会穿过你的身体
They will not pass through your body,
因为它们不存在
for they do not exist.
它们不存在
They do not exist.
不真实
Unreal.
只是表象
Appearances only.
他们是影子，假象
They are shadows. Illusions.
只是现实的幽灵
Nothing but ghosts of reality.
他们是谎言，谎言
They are lies. Falsehoods.
没有实体的幽灵
Spectres without body.
忽略他们
They are to be ignored.
舰长
Captain.
拔枪吧
Draw.
舰长，我…不明白
Captain, I... don't understand.
我也没有，他非常jian健康 kang
Neither do I. He's in perfect health.
- 我去哪儿了？  - 似乎就在这里
- Where have I been? - Right here, it seems.
但是那个女孩，她是如此美丽，太真实了
But that girl. She was so beautiful. So real.
- 你还记得别的吗？  - 没有了
- Do you remember anything else? - No.
这就解释了他为什么会在这里，什么都不是真的，除了那女孩
That explains why he was here. Nothing was real to him except the girl.
舰长，梅尔克特物体
Captain, the Melkotian object.
传感器读数
Sensor readings.
该物体正在发射极不稳定的射线
The object is emitting rays of a highly unstable nature.
拉响红色警报，偏转护盾全开
Sound Red Alert. Deflector shields on full.
枪手们，锁定目标
Gun crews, lock on target.
能量输出增加超过可测量的水平
Energy output increasing beyond measurable levels.
相位枪，待命开火
Phaser guns, stand by to fire.
它……它不见了，长官
It's... It's gone, sir.
- 损坏报告  - 没有，所有甲板全面运作
- Damage report. - None. All decks fully operational.
梅尔克特：柯克舰长
MELKOT: Captain Kirk.
你没有杀人
You did not kill.
- 这是你们种族的处理方式吗？  - 是的
- Is this the way of your kind? - It is.
我们只有在别无选择的时候才会战斗，我们更喜欢和平
We fight only when there's no choice. We prefer peace.
我代表一个相信同样事物的生物联盟
I speak for an alliance of creatures who believe in the same thing.
我们已邀请你们加入我们，我们的使命是和平
We have sought you out to join us. Our mission is one of peace.
靠近我们的星球，欢迎你们，代表团会出来迎接你
Approach our planet. Be welcome. A delegation will come out to meet you.
我们的警告威胁已经结束
Our warning threats are over.
好极了，上尉，取消红色警报
Excellent. Lieutenant, cancel Red Alert.
- 继续原航线，曲速2  - 曲速2，长官
- Resume original course, warp 2. - Warp factor 2, sir.
舰长，我可以问个问题吗？如果太私人了，你不必回答
Captain, may I ask a question? You needn't answer if it's too personal.
我确定我能回答
I'm sure I'll be able to answer.
今天下午，你想杀人，是吗？
This afternoon, you wanted to kill, didn't you?
- 但他没有杀人，史波克先生  - 但他想，医生
- But he didn't kill, Mr. Spock. - But he wanted to, Doctor.
- 在你看来是这样吗？  - 是的，舰长
- Is that the way it seemed to you? - Yes, Captain.
史波克先生，你说得很对，事实也正是如此
Mr. Spock, you're absolutely right. That's exactly the way it was.
人类，准备杀戮
Mankind, ready to kill.
那是1881年的情况了
That's the way it was in 1881.
我想知道人类是如何生存下来的
I wonder how humanity managed to survive.
我们克服了暴力的本能
We overcame our instinct for violence.